there's two things that have made college
significantly less valuable.
So thing number one is that the education
that you get at college is for sure inferior now
to free alternatives.
Like that was like maybe arguable and is now definitive.
Like an AI tutor that can do whatever you want
in real time is more valuable.
On the other side from a cost basis,
it for sure doesn't fucking make any sense
because you can get a better thing for less.
So like now there's that part.
And so then the only thing that people make the argument
for for college is that it forces networking
for people who are in lower,
who start with lower socioeconomic status
to network with people with higher socioeconomic status.
That is maybe the only thing,
but I mean like there's platforms like school and whatnot
that can bring communities together.
But the last piece is like, okay,
well do you have higher earning power?
Which is literally just not true anymore.
Like you don't have higher earning power
as a result of being a college graduate.
And so the value proposition is just,
is you don't get more educated,
you don't get better job prospects,
it costs money and take longer.
And I think that that has just gotten
more and more extreme in the past four years.
And I think that that will accelerate.
Like if you're 18 years old right now,
there's very little point in saying I wanna become a doctor.
Like by the time that you graduate eight years from now
and then you finish your residency 10 years from now,
whatever it is,
like there will be surgical robots
and diagnostic robots right now
that will just, that will literally beat humans at everything.
And we can say whatever we want.
When it comes to health,
I think people are gonna be like,
I would choose human,
but I'm gonna choose the thing that gets me to die less.